xegen.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Xegen.com - Xegen, Video and full entertainment portal

By using any of the services on Xegen.com, you agree to abide by this privacy policy. 

All information available on this site is publically available. So it is recommended that you do not put any personally identifiable information online. Xegen.com or any of its businesses (online or offline) are not liable to keep any of this information private. 

Some of the information shared by you like email and SMS will also be used to communicate to you occasionally about our new products or promos which we think may be of your interest. You can opt out from such a communications by writing to us at unsubscribe@Xegen.com or admin@Xegen.com. 

Xegen.com also tracks some of the user’s non-personally identifiable data like cookies, sessions, web beacons, IP address, etc. for various business reasons including but not limited to advertising, tracking, reporting, etc. 

In addition, third party affiliates may place and read cookies on your browsers, or use other means to collect information as a result of ad serving on this website. 

It is recommended to view these policies monthly to ensure you are well versed with changes if any. 

Xegen.com can change the policies from time to time for business, legal, customer satisfaction reasons. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
